YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
■
时间轴：   Noodle
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  非燕  阿蘅  独醉  YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二集
天啊  我宿醉还没过去
Oh, God, guys, I'm still really hungover.
我真的毁了一场婚礼吗
Did I really ruin a wedding?
没有  你没毁了婚礼
No, you didn't ruin a wedding.
只有接待处而已
Just the reception.
还有隔壁的犹太成年礼
And the bar mitzvah next door.
还有我的裙子
And my dress.
还有你的裙子  你一度穿了条裙子
And your dress. You put on a dress at one point.
好了  到此为止
Okay, you know what, that's it.
我就要当爸爸了  我要成为
I'm about to be a dad, and I want to be
让我孩子崇拜的男人
the kind of man that my child can look up to.
所以在此郑重宣布
So, sweeping declaration--
我此生再也不喝醉了
I am never getting drunk again as long as I live.
我说真的
I'm serious.
孩子们  你们的马修叔叔
Kids, it's not that your Uncle Marshall
并不嗜酒
had a drinking problem.
只是他每次像那样郑重宣布
But whenever he made a sweeping declaration like that,
结果你们也都清楚
you pretty much knew...
第二天
我又醉了
I did it again.
这件事回头再细说
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
你的腿怎么了
What happened to your leg?
没事
Oh, nothing.
我约了诺拉喝咖啡
I'm meeting Nora for coffee.
她还在生我的气  所以我需要装可怜
She's still mad at me, so I need some sympathy points.
她喜欢音乐剧  所以我准备告诉她
She likes musicals, so I'm going to tell her
我在表演《堂吉诃德》的时候
I fell off the stage
不慎从舞台上摔下来了
during a performance of Man of La Mancha.
你们觉得呢
What do you think?
别提演员的事
Lose the cast.
单人剧目啊  我喜欢
A one-man show-- I like it!
《堂吉诃德》是群舞剧目
我们先理理思路
Just so we're clear--
这个女人生你气是因为你对她撒谎
this woman is mad at you because you lied to her.
而你的解决方法  是假装摔坏腿博同情吗
So your solution is to pretend you broke your leg?
你说的对
You're right.
应该加个护颈  多谢  莉莉
A neck brace. Thanks, Lil.
天  我早点问你们就好了
Man, I wish I'd have talked to you sooner.
我这一整天都在练习使用这副拐杖
I've been practicing with these crutches all day
把它们落在我楼道的人
and whoever left them in my lobby
现在应该非常需要它们吧
probably really needs 'em.
我有好消息
Well, uh, I have some good news.
你们都知道  我最近决定重振旗鼓
As you all know, I recently decided to get back out there
开始约会了  然后
and start dating again. And, uh, well...
这是你吗
Is this you?
是啊  你好
Uh, yeah. Hi.
我是泰德
I'm Ted.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
这太好了  泰德
That's great, Ted.
是啊是啊  这纯粹是机缘巧合
Yeah. Yeah, it was a moment of pure destiny.
绝对不是我故意去创造的
The kind you just can't manufacture.
或许只是我的个人看法
Or so I thought.
哇  我居然成了封面人物
Oh, no. How did I get on there?
你好  我是泰德・莫斯比
Hi. Ted Mosby.
有罪啊
Guilty.
嗨  泰德・莫斯比
Hi. Ted Mosby.
真是太难为情了
That is embarrassing.
我应该当《尴尬一刻》的封面人物
I should be on the cover of Egg On My Face magazine.
可我没有
But I'm not.
我是被印在了这本
I'm on the cover of this one.
嗨  泰德・莫斯比
Hi. Ted Mosby.
一天内  16次机缘巧合
16 moments of pure destiny in one day,
在这16人中  有10人是单身
and of those 16,ten were single.
这10人中  有7人对我有好感
Of those ten, seven liked what they saw.
在这7人中  有4人是女性
Of those seven,four were women.
在这4人中  有2人给我了真实号码
Of those four,two gave me their real number.
然后我成功约到了她们俩
And I have a date with both of them.
太好了
Okay.
各位  是加里森・库兹打来的
Guys,it's Garrison Cootes.
孩子们  加里森・库兹是
Kids, Garrison Cootes was a senior partner
哈尼维尔/库兹公司的高级合伙人
at Honeywell & Cootes.
此公司是美国最大的保护环境律所
One of the biggest environmental law firms in America.
马修为了供职与此  愿意不惜一切
Marshall would have given anything to work there.
如果我得不到这份工作  我也许沦为
If I don't get this job, I might end up working
玉米卷快餐店的小工
at, like, a Taco Bell somewhere.
谁也不想这样
And nobody wants that.
不过也许正合你们心意
Or maybe you guys want that,
因为那样你们就有免费玉米卷吃了
because you'll get free tacos,
毕竟你们是我的好朋友
'cause your my peeps.
但是现在我需要你们所有人冷静下来
But right now I need all of you to calm down!
您好
Hello.
马修  我是加里森・库兹
Marshall, this is Garrison Cootes.
抱歉我没能及时回复你
Sorry I didn't get back to you sooner,
我最近老抽不开身
but I've just been swamped.
这太好笑了  因为我现在真的
Which is funny, 'cause I'm literally
身处一片沼泽里  抽不开身
standing in a swamp.
总之  我来这儿采集一些
Anyway, I'm just out here, I'm just collecting some samples
我们调查的污染案要用的取样
for this pollution case we're working on.
我喜欢你们的工作
I love the work you guys do.
有条鳄鱼[双关语有假话的意思]
That's a croc...
不  我说真的
No, I mean it.
不不  真有条鳄鱼  离我五步远
No, no, there's a crocodile about five feet away from me.
所以我准备忽略我们对话期间
So I'm just going to ignore the hot urine
有泡热腾腾的尿灌满了我的靴子
filling my waders as we speak,
我只想告诉你  我们对你很感兴趣
and tell you that we're very interested.
他很感兴趣
He's interested.
显然我们还要做一些信誉度
Obviously we have to do some sort of credit check,
犯罪记录和网络搜索等调查
you know, a criminal record and Google search,
只要不出现什么不堪入目的事情
but as long as nothing unseemly turns up,
你就准备入职吧  伙计
you're good to go, man.
这太好了  库兹先生
That is fantastic, Mr. Cootes!
我先挂了
Well, I gotta run.
真是太好笑了
This is so funny,
因为如果我再不跑就真的要挂了
because, actually, I physically have to run now.
-鳄鱼看见你了  -是啊  它在向我逼近
- Croc saw you? - He's advancing, yeah.
第二天晚上  巴尼约了诺拉喝咖啡
The next night, Barney met Nora for coffee.
谢天谢地  他放弃了拄拐博同情的戏码
Thankfully, without the ridiculous leg cast.
诺拉  谢谢你来见我
Hey, Nora, thanks for meeting me here.
你脖子怎么了
What happened to your neck?
我  哦  没事
My wha...? Oh, it's nothing.
我当时正在表演单人剧目《屋顶上的小提琴手》
I was performing in a one-man show of Fiddler.
然后不幸从屋顶摔下来了
There was this roof.
哇  那人有一对绝世好咪
Wow, that one has fantastic ta-tas.
什么  哪里
What, where?
完蛋  暴露了
Oh... Oh, damn it.
再见
Ta-ta.
等等  诺拉  等等  别走
Wait, Nora, wait... No, look, please don't.
抱歉  真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你这是怎么回事
What is the matter with you?
什么样的人才需要撒这种谎
What kind of person needs to lie like that.
一个真心喜欢你的人
A person who really, really likes you.
或许更确切地说  是一个怀疑
And suspects, probably accurately,
自己配不上你的人
that you're way out of his league,
所以他觉得有必要
and so he feels the need to...
抱歉  你刚才说的绝世好咪  是开玩笑的吧
I'm sorry, you were kidding about the fantastic ta-tas, right?
因为我扫完一遍  都没看见
'Cause I'm looking around and I do not see 'em...
我刚才连续赴了两个约会
I just had two back-to-back dates.
没错  和两位可爱的女人
That's right, two lovely ladies,
喝了四大杯卡布奇诺  还有
four large cappuccinos, and...
马上回来
one sec.
两分钟后
我不确定哪个更好
And I don't know which date was more awesome.
我来介绍一下她们吧
Let's meet the girls.
杰西卡是个领罗氏奖学金的研究生
Jessica is a Rhodes scholar.
罗氏奖学金是英国大学历史最长并且也是声誉最高的奖学金
她周游了世界列国
She's traveled all over the world.
会说四种语言  还是个职业钢琴演奏家
Speaks four languages, is a concert pianist.
而克莱尔则主动买单
And Claire reached for the check.
所以我也不知道
So I don't know.
差距好微弱哦
It's a squeaker.
这两个女孩
I mean, both of these girls
都是潜力股
have the potential to be something really special.
-她俩同时晋级了  -等等
- They both move on to the next round. - Wait a minute.
你是准备脚踏两条船吗
You're going to date two girls at once?
难道你不觉得应该在正式恋爱之前
Don't you think you should just choose one
先选好一个吗
before it gets serious?
什么算正式恋爱
Define serious.
一言难尽
Well, that's complicated.
你得先权衡期望值
I guess you have to weigh expectations,
感情投资
emotional investments...
三垒
Third base.
上了三垒就算
Seriously, third base.
所以我和这两个女孩能上到二垒  对吧
So I can go to second base with both of these girls, no problem?
放手做吧  朋友  放手去做
Oh, honk away, my friend. Yeah, honk away.
不是吧
Oh, no.
自从库兹先生提出要调查背景后
Ever since Mr. Cootes mentioned the background check,
马修就一直在刷网页
Marshall had been scouring the Internet.
他发现大部分都无伤大雅的小玩笑
Most of what he found was pretty harmless.
有的还特别赞  直到...
In some cases, really awesome, until...
不妙
Not good.
这下不妙了
This-- this is not good.
谢了  史黛西
Thanks, Stacy.
卫斯利大学开了家新的自助餐厅
Wesleyan has a new cafeteria,
感谢捐助这笔丰厚善款的
thanks to the generous endowment from--
刚才是说有人慷慨解囊吗
Did somebody say generous endowment?
我是马修・埃里克森  也可以叫我啤酒猛男里斯
I'm Marshall Eriksen, but you can call me Beercules!
随便嫁祸给一个路人就好啦
Well, that could be anybody.
伙计  我居然忘了啤酒猛男里斯的事
Oh, man, I forgot about Beercules.
话说这个网站是谁做的
Who made this Web site anyway?
-皮特・钥仙  -难怪
- Pete Durkenson.- Of course.
是那个人说服你裸奔校园的吗
Is that the guy who convinced you to run across campus naked?
我当时正申请加入他的兄弟会
I was pledging his frat,
不过三天后我就放弃了
which I gave up on after three days,
因为兄弟会里鱼龙混杂
because frats are stupid and elitist
而且我发现他不是兄弟会的成员
and also I found out he wasn't in a frat.
天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God.This is awesome.
我刚接到建筑师舞会的邀请
I just got invited to the Architects' Ball,
这是为全市最棒的建筑师举行的年会
the annual gala that honors the city's greatest architects.
天  你们知道这事的弊端了吧
Oh, no, you guys see why this sucks, right?
因为这年会是
Because it's an annual gala
为全市最棒的建筑师举行的吗
honoring the city's greatest architects?
罗宾  这是年度社交活动
Robin, this is the social event of the year.
如果你带女伴去参加了这次盛会
You take a girl to the Architects' Ball,
兄弟  你今晚绝对能上三垒
brother, you're going to third base.
不管我选谁做我的女伴
Whichever girl I take as my date,
她都会在今晚前
she will be Miss Ted Mosby's girlfriend
成为泰德・莫斯比的女友
by the end of the night.
好  不能再举棋不定了
Okay, no more sitting on the fence.
罗宾  把我的拍纸簿拿来
Robin, get me my legal pad.
二选一时间
It's pros and cons time!
孩子们  这是发自内心的欢呼
And kids, they really cheered.
有件事我要说清楚
Let me make one thing very clear to you.
我不和撒谎骗我的人约会
I don't date guys who lie to me.
你看  我事先不知道
Well, see, I did not know that.
我的错
My bad.
从现在起  我不会撒谎了
So, from here on in, no more lies.
我不会再骗你了
I will never lie to you again.
我是认真的  不信你试试
I'm serious. Ask me anything.
好
Okay.
你有没有成功
Have you ever successfully
骗到女人上床
gotten a woman in bed by lying to her?
我有没有
Have I ever...
如果我完全坦诚
If I'm being totally honest...
有
Yes.
不止一次
More than once?
More than once...
这真是
Wow, that's...
我想如果我们斤斤计较
I guess if we're splitting hairs,
然后就会涉及到我说了多少次谎
Then, technically... there was a plurality
来骗一个女人上床
to the times I've lied to women for sex having purposes.
多少次
What were they?
大部分是九次或者十次
Nines and tens mostly.
只有一回是四次
There was a four once.
她是个丑八怪
She was a slump buster.
但是之后  我连续得手的次数肯定会让你大吃一惊
But, Nora, after that, I had a run that you would not believe.
天啊  诚实的感觉真好
Man, honesty feels good.
你撒的都是什么谎
What were the lies?
你想知道  我为了哄女人上床
You want me to tell you every lie I've ever told a woman
而撒的每一个谎吗
to get her into bed?
只要骗到她们跟你发生关系的谎  我都要听
A bed or any other place you had sex with her.
你果然够醒目
Oh, you're good.
皮特  皮特  你好
Pete, Pete. Hey.
啤酒猛男里斯
Beercules!
来抱一个  老兄
Bring it in, dude.
我一直在给你打电话
Hey, I've been trying to call you,
打了一整晚了
like, all night.
我的天  对不起
Oh, my God, sorry.
我本来可以接的  但是今天是周二之夜
I would have answered, but it is Tuesday night.
今天是周日
It's Sunday.
你知道那意味着什么
And you know what that means.
"爱德华啤酒手"
"Edward Forty Hands."
孩子们  这是个游戏
Kids, "Edward Forty Hands"
把两瓶四十盎司的麦芽酒
is a game that involves taping two 40-ounce bottles
绑在你的双手上
of malt liquor to your hands.
任务就是喝完两瓶酒
The object is to finish both bottle--
天啊  我什么要告诉你们这些
Oh, my God, why am I telling you this?
我们继续主题
Let's move on.
你知道我裸奔的那个视频吧
Okay, you know that old video of me streaking?
我每天都温习
I watch it every day.
麻烦你把视频从网上删了吧
Well, I need you to take it down off the Internet.
比如  就现在
Like, right now.
现在你有两个选择
There are two ways that can happen.
要么你给我四百万
One, you can give me $4 million,
要么你在我上厕所的时候搭把手
or... you can help me go to the bathroom,
因为  我不能
because I... I can't...
不  这两个选择都没得商量
Yeah, those are two non-negotiable no's.
很遗憾我们没能达成交易
Well, I'm sorry we could not do business together.
如果你不介意
But if you'll excuse me,
我正在玩"爱德华啤酒手"
I'm in the middle of a game of "Edward Forty Hands,"
比赛很激烈
and the competition is fierce.
你和谁玩呢
Who are you playing with, anyway?
自娱自乐
Just myself.
与此同时  巴尼继续把他骗女孩上床的
Meanwhile, Barney continued listing every lie
伎俩全数抖出
he'd ever told to get laid.
没时间解释我为什么被咬了
There's no time to explain how I got bit there.
我需要有人帮我把毒吸出来
I just need someone to suck the poison out.
外科医生给我换了一张新面孔
The surgeons gave me a new face,
亲爱的
honey.
我还活着  你不开心吗
Aren't you relieved I'm alive?
我是大卫・贝克汉姆
Me llamo David Beckham.
如果我来选《白天鹅》的演员
If I were only casting The White Swan
女主角绝对是你
the role would be yours.
不  我是个拉拉
No, I am a lesbian.
只不过我身上戴的某个器官实在是太栩栩如生了
This thing that I'm wearing is just really lifelike.
行了  这些都跳过
Okay, let's skip ahead.
最坏的是哪一次
What's the worst one?
毫无下限
The lowest of the low?
怪异之极的那次
The creme de la creepy?
有一次我利用电影《灵魂歌手》来泡妞
Uh... Oh, I once pulled The Soul Man.
因为有个美女  她只跟黑人约会
There was this beautiful girl who only dated black guys...
巴奈尔  我就知道
Barnell! Ooh, I knew it!
我无法抉择
I can't decide.
她们都很棒
They're both awesome.
要是建筑师有两个舞会就好了  对吧
If only architects had two balls, right, Ted?
引申义  要是您这大建筑师有勇气抉择就好了
我有办法
I got this.
泰德  左还是右
Ted, left or right?
对对  好主意
Yes, yes, great idea.
交给命运来抉择吧
Let the fates decide, huh?
我选左边
I will pick left.
随便打给其中一个
Just call one of 'em.
泰德  在你的内心深处
Ted, deep in your heart,
你知道你更喜欢的是谁
you know that you kind of like one more than the other.
相信我  带另一个去
Trust me-- take the other.
我可能没说清楚  这是
Um, maybe I haven't been clear: this is...
建筑师舞会  罗宾
the Architects' Ball, Robin.
众星云集啊
It's a star-studded event.
哪个名人会去啊
Okay, name one celebrity who's gonna be there.
蓝尼・克罗维兹
Uh... Lenny Kravitz.
蓝尼・克罗维兹会去
Lenny Kravitz is gonna be there?
是啊  他每年都来
Yeah. He's there every year.
那家伙可是个摇滚明星呢
And that guy's a rock star.
泰德  我一直在想
You know, Ted, I've been thinking--
现在让你在这两个女孩中做决定  有点为时过早
it's too soon to narrow it down between these two girls.
带一个朋友去吧
Just take a friend.
我不知道  或许你可以带
Like I... I don't know, maybe, uh, a friend
家里有蓝尼・克罗维兹海报的那个吧
who had a poster of Lenny Kravitz on her wall,
也许她的整个高中时期
and may or may not have, perhaps,
和那海报分分合合  把它黏上撕下了无数次
dated that poster, on and off, throughout high school.
这个利弊列表没什么用处
This pros and cons list isn't cutting it.
我要一个彩色图表
I need a color chart.
彩色图表  彩色图表
Color chart! Color chart!
孩子们  这是发自内心的欢唱
And, kids, we all really chanted.
皮特  求你了
Pete, please.
我待业家中
I'm unemployed.
还有巨额贷款
I have a huge mortgage.
我的孩子马上就要降临人世
I have a baby on the way.
而现在  我却要因为十五年前的一个玩笑
And now, I'm about to lose a job I really need
失去一份我急需的工作
because of a 15-year-old prank!
你听到你自己说的话了么
Ugh! Do you hear yourself?
啤酒猛男里斯  你怎么了
Beercules, what happened?
你完全不一样了
You're like a different person.
视频里那人好棒
The guy in that video was awesome.
他潜力无限
He had potential.
他还可能当上兄弟会的老大哦
He could have been president of the frat one day.
根本就没什么兄弟会
There was no frat!
现在他就一扫兴鬼
Now he's just a bummer.
我并不想做扫兴鬼
It's not like I want to be a bummer.
我只是  不得已而为之
I just... I have to be.
我要做父亲了
I'm gonna be a dad.
你以后也会有孩子的
You'll have kids someday.
那时你就会明白我的心情
You'll understand.
兄弟  哥有四孩子
Dude, I have four kids.
皮特  请你把视频删掉吧
Pete, please take the video down.
好的  啤酒猛男里斯 我会把视频删掉
All right, Beercules, I'll take the video down.
如果
If...
你能在我指定的比赛中胜过我
you can best me in a game of my own choosing.
不是吧
Oh, no...
我选择精彩之战
And I select the beautiful game,
动人之技
the sweet science...
皮特  拜托  我还宿醉未醒呢
Pete, please, I'm so hungover...
王者之拼
...the sport of kings...
我不想玩"爱德华啤酒手"
I don't want to play "Edward Forty Hands."
我本来想说飞镖
I was gonna say darts--
那就比"爱德华啤酒手"吧
but "Edward Forty Hands" it is!
以上是太空相关谎言
And that concludes all the space-related lies.
再来说运动方面的
Let's move on to the world of sports.
等等  我刚想起还有一个太空的
Oh, wait, sorry-- I just thought of another space one.
我被月球上的蛇咬了
"I've been bitten by a moon snake.
你得吸光我的太空之毒
You need to suck all the space poison out of my--"
好了  巴尼
Okay, Barney, uh,
我明天八点得上班
I have to be at work tomorrow at 8:00,
如果我现在就走
which means I have just about enough time
整好够时间泡11个小时的澡  安慰自己受伤的心灵
to sit in a shower for 11 hours, hugging myself.
咱们聊得挺开心的
So this was fun.
我再打给你还是...
Can I call you, or...?
巴尼  你风趣  帅气
Barney, you're funny, handsome
非常聪明
and really quite clever.
但同时你也是个毫无良知的人
But you're also a sociopath.
三个优点比一个缺点  那
Well, I count three pros and one con, so...
为什么你会觉得和我还有机会呢
How do you still think you have a chance with me?
因为你听我说了一晚
Because you sat here all night.
你可以马上走的  但你没有
You could've left right away, but you didn't.
诺拉  那些谎言  都是过去的我
Look, Nora, all those lies-- that's the old me.
我向你发誓  我在试图改变
But I swear to you, I am trying to change.
是你  让我想改变
You... make me want to change.
我如何知道这不是个谎言
How do I know that's not a lie?
我会向你证明
I'll prove it.
我会向你证明我有多认真
I will prove how serious I am.
我不会离开这家餐厅
I will not leave this diner
除非你答应再跟我约会
until I get a second date with you.
再见  巴尼
Good-bye, Barney.
我没开玩笑哦
I'm not kidding.
这家餐厅24小时营业
This is a 24-hour diner.
我会永远待在这里  如果必须的话  我会的
I'll stay here forever, if I have to-- and I will!
来杯水就行  谢谢
Just water for me. Thanks.
好了  红色代表吸引力
Okay, so red indicates level of attractiveness,
蓝色  智力激发
blue-- intellectual stimulation,
绿色  情感沟通
green-- emotional connection,
黄色  人生目标的和谐性
yellow-- compatibility of life goals,
紫色  有没有抢着买单
and purple-- whether or not she reached for the check.
看来杰西卡领先了
Well, it looks like Jessica's ahead
前四项
in the first four categories.
有没有抢着买单
Did not reach for the check...
这件礼服吗
Oh, this?
没什么大不了的
No big deal. This...
虽然价值三个月房租
This cost three months rent,
可惜没机会穿
and, uh, I've never gotten to wear it,
我之所以会买  是因为你邀请我参加一个隆重的场合
because I bought it for that big event that you invited me to,
可惜最终泡汤了
which then fell through.
可你知道吗
But, you know what?
你不用感到内疚哦
Don't feel guilty about that.
什么场合
What big event?
为你叔叔举办的
That thing with your uncle.
他的葬礼吗
His funeral?
那可不是泡汤
It didn't fall through,
是他奇迹般地苏醒了好不好
he miraculously came out of a coma.
我原谅你了
And I forgive you.
现在  我能够有机会见蓝尼・克罗维兹吗
Now, can I please meet Lenny Kravitz?
我又喝醉了
I did it again!
亲爱的
Aw, honey.
你又喝醉了
You got drunk again.
真不敢相信我居然下注他不再犯
I can't believe I took the over.
申明下  就我当前醉酒的情况而言
Just to be clear, "I did it again" is not a reference...
"我又喝醉了"这句话没那么简单
to my current state of inebriation.
那是有多复杂
What's it a reference to?
我叫马修・埃里克森
My name is Marshall Eriksen.
现年33岁
I'm 33 years old.
如果我的未来老板  加里森・库兹
And if my potential future employer, Garrison Cootes,
在看这个
is watching this...
向啤酒猛男里斯鞠躬吧
bow down to Beercules!
随便嫁祸给一个路人就好啦
Well, that could be anybody.
天啊
Oh, goodness.
皮特  我是莉莉・艾得仁
Pete, this is Lily Aldrin.
我就开门见山了
I'm gonna make this real simple:
你要删掉马修的视频
You're gonna take down that video of Marshall.
知道为什么吗
You know why?
你在大学时约会的三个女生  都是我的朋友
Because I'm friends with three girls who dated you in college,
女生之间是无话不谈的
and girls tell each other everything.
连任何一个"小"细节都不放过
Every tiny detail.
所以
Huh. So...
滴答滴答  皮特  小老二的钟要敲响咯
tick-tock, Pete-- tick-tock goes the little wee-wee clock.
皮特的老二很小吗
Pete's got a little wee-wee?
不知道  大家都点了什么
No idea. What's everyone getting?
这事注定是要发生的
This was bound to happen eventually.
我一直拼命压制
I've been trying so hard to suppress, like,
自己快活无知的一面
my carefree idiot side,
可越压制越爆发
that it just rebelled and came out swingin'!
的确如此
It sure did.
快看我  我是人体风车
Look at me! I'm a windmill!
我骗谁呀  我果然不够格当爸爸
Who am I kidding? I'm not ready to be a dad.
我曾一度觉得我可以  但
I thought that I was, but it's, like...
我爸爸就从来不会干这种傻事
my dad never did stuff like that, you know?
如果他做过呢
So what if he did?
你依然那么爱他
You'd still love him.
老实说  难道你不想偶然发现一个视频
And be honest-- wouldn't you love to stumble onto a video
是你自己老爸全裸狂奔在大街上  大声嚷道
of him running down the street naked, yelling,
马修  快看我
"Hey, Marshall, look at me!
我的大腿内侧有一根大冰柱
I got an icicle on my deal!"
各位好啊
Oh! Hey, guys!
哎呦  我的脖子
Ow! My neck!
你们看
Look at that.
巴尼  你在这儿干嘛
Barney, what are you doing here?
我告诉诺拉  除非她愿意跟我再次约会
Oh, I told Nora I wouldn't leave
否则我要一直呆在这儿
until she gave me a second date,
我可是很认真的哦
and I mean it.
我已经在这儿呆了九个小时了
I've already been here nine hours.
再给我点时间考虑考虑
I still need another minute.
可能你们会觉得我很疯狂  但是
I mean... call me crazy, but
我一定要在这儿  把那个女孩等回来
I'm gonna stay here until I get that girl back.
那  那就是我想要的
That-- that's what I want.
巴尼对诺拉的执着
The way Barney feels about Nora--
我想重拾那份执着
I want that feeling again.
我不想在两个女孩间摇摆不定
I don't want to be choosing between two girls,
我想为了一个女孩  成为彻头彻尾的傻瓜
I want to be... a complete head-over-heels idiot for one.
对  成为彻头彻尾的傻瓜
Yeah, the complete head-over-heels idiot thing's
也挺好
pretty nice.
是不错
It's not bad.
虽然如此  还是要报备一下
Although, for the record--
决定性的重大宣告
sweeping declaration!--
我再也不会喝醉酒了
I am never getting drunk again.
结果当然是
And sure enough...
向啤酒猛男里斯致敬吧
All hail Beercules!
太棒了
Yeah!
这件事也留着下次再细说吧
But, again, I'm getting ahead of myself.
你好
Hello.
马修  我是加里森・库兹
Marshall! Garrison Cootes.
是的  库兹先生
Yes, Mr. Cootes.
嗨  你好
Hi. How are you?
我是来通知你  我们的背景调查完成了
I just wanted to let you know, we did the background check,
这个分层真让人心烦哪[streaking有裸奔的意思]
and that is some disturbing streaking.
马修理解为  他发现了一些有碍风化的裸奔视频
先生  这是其实是
Sir, th-th-the thing is, um...
这个取样出现的彩虹分层
The rainbow streaking in this sample
肯定是化学径流所致
is definitely from chemical runoff.
我
Oh, I...
总之  我们欢迎你的加入
Bottom line-- we'd love to have you on board.
太棒了
That is fantastic!
谢谢你  库兹先生
Thank you, Mr. Cootes!
不用客气
Well, you're welcome.
对了  当你来上班时
And-- oh, and when you're at the office,
麻烦把衣服穿上  啤酒猛男里斯
try to wear some clothes, okay, Beercules?
哇  是条大蟒
Wow! That's a big snake.
沼泽里有条大蟒吗
Oh, there's a snake in the swamp?
不  我是在说你的老二
No, I'm talking about your penis.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
我录取了
I got the job.
好耶
Yay!
我觉得我的老板刚在性骚扰我
And I think that my boss already sexually harassed me.
但是他看了视频  他却不当一回事
But he saw the video and he doesn't care!
看吧  啤酒猛男里斯也没那么糟嘛
See that? Maybe Beercules isn't so bad after all.
对
Yeah.
你好
Hello?
马修  我叫皮特・钥仙
Hey, Marshall, my name is Pete Durkenson.
我们当年一起在卫斯利念大学
We went to Wesleyan together.
是  我知道
Yeah, no, I know.
皮特  我们昨天还一起喝酒来着
Pete, we... we just hung out yesterday.
好吧  我明白为什么会收到莉莉的留言了
All right, now Lily's message makes a little more sense.
听着  别担心  兄弟
Listen, don't worry, bro,
我会把视频撤下来的
I'm gonna take down the video.
你知道吗
You know what?
算了吧
Leave it up.
那随你咯  啤酒猛男里斯
Whatever you say, Beercules.
解剖刀
Scalpel.
其实这也不错
You know what? This is good.
我想让我的孩子看到我的多面性
I want our kid to see every side of who I am.
对
Yeah.
即使是带着喝醉的脑子
Even the side that runs through
裸奔向东村区的那一面
the East Village hangin' brain.
我还是打电话给皮特好了
I'm gonna call Pete back.
这个主意不错
That's a good idea.
那晚我带罗宾去参加建筑师年会
That evening, I took Robin to the Architects' Ball.
再次感谢你能带我来
Thanks again for taking me to this.
乐意之极
My pleasure.
或许你会觉得很有趣也说不定
And, you know, you might find it interesting.
是啊是啊  蓝尼・克罗维兹在哪里
Yeah, yeah. Where's Lenny Kravitz?
那里
Right there.
蓝尼・克罗维兹  世界闻名的建筑大师
Leonard Kravitz, world-renowned architect.
他就是个不朽的明星
Guy's a rock star.
他准备发表著名的
He's gonna be giving his famous
关于横梁的90分钟演说
90-minute lecture on crossbeams.
真是太棒了
Well, great.
我真想找根横梁  吊死自己算了
I'm gonna go find one and hang myself from it.
好吧
Okay.
孩子们  你们无法说服自己去恋爱
Kids, you can't talk yourself into falling in love.
爱情是无需浪费时间去深思熟虑
It doesn't take days of deliberation.
只要是真爱  你立刻便能知晓
When it's real, you know pretty quickly,
并且坚信不移
and with absolute certainty.
我忘记了那种感觉
I had forgotten that.
但记忆即将被唤醒
But I was about to be reminded.
维多利亚 *
* Victoria
* Victoria...